Mastodon Account Audit Trails
For the ASYLUM-JOURNEY Threads Account
======================================

This Git repository contains audit trail logging of the "asylumjourney" Threads account, which is visible on the Mastodon federverse as a compatible account with username @asylumjourney@threads.net.

The account was configured to enable the "Fediverse sharing" functionality, which means that the account is compliant with Mastodon's technical requirements, and profile, posts and other actions made on the account can be accessed by Mastodon instances.

The purpose of setting up this account is to document Li Ao's journey in exile seeking international protection, as being a person owing to fairness of being prosecuted by the Chinese government as he holds certain kinds of political opinion which is targeted by government's increasing use of restrictive measures against the citizens. Additionally, another purpose to seek asylum is because of the increasingly deteriorating situations of China on many matters related to human rights.