On 23/10/2025 at 1pm the following plain text contents were requested for posting on the Threads webapp, with each of the posts being consolidated together to becoming a thread:

#1:	(1/3) Hello all, I'm Li Ao a Chinese national being in exile in Malaysia currently for seeking international protection.

	I dismissed my house permanently in December 2024 and became homeless thereafter. Up until now, I've been homeless for over 10 months.

	Because of backlogs of UNHCR's Malaysia office even registration, which is supposed to become the first step of seeking international protection under the UNHCR framework, needs an appointment which requires a long time until getting a

#2:	(2/3) schedule, so during this time I need to invigorate myself, and to keeping up until this eventually happens.

	Starting from now I will occasionally post my stories online, and on the 1st anniversary of being homeless I will start writing journals for the beginning of my journey.

	Internet is my companion, with it I can see this beautiful world, and my favorite Western companies I appreciate them the most as they opened up the world to me, so that I know how Western values helped me to gain

#3:	(3/3) resiliency and resistence against the inhumane treatment of the Chinese Communist Party.

	So, please stay tuned and follow me if interested!